Every day we have a chance to dream big again
매일 우리는 다시 크게 꿈꿀 수 있습니다
and make it happen, right?
그리고 그 꿈을 현실로 만들 기회가 있습니다
What brings me the most joy and passion about this
제가 일을 하면서 가장 큰 즐거움과 열정을 느끼는 부분은...
is the idea of one table, one team.
‘하나의 테이블, 하나의 팀’이라는 개념입니다
Dreaming by myself is just a dream,
혼자 꾸는 꿈은 그저 꿈이지만
but dreaming together is the reality
함께 꾸는 꿈은 현실이 됩니다
Using the SOBABA technology to make the chicken more crispy,
한국 소바바의 기술력을 차용하여 치킨의 바삭함을 극대화했고
and then adding a new sauce flavor for that authenticity.
여기에 한국 정통의 새로운 소스 맛을 입혔습니다
And then, we have with egg roll, the gochujang works great,
에그롤을 판매할 때 고추장 소스를 곁들이면 궁합이 완벽하며
or any type of to-go execution with a mandu
만두를 테이크아웃 형태로 판매할 때도
works great with the gochujang.
이 고추장 소스는 엄청난 시너지를 냅니다
It has a lot of technology
엄청난 R&D 기술의 집약체입니다
@@largest microwaveable pizza.
세계 최초이자, 규격 면에서도 역대 가장 큰 사이즈의 전자레인지용 피자입니다
The spicy-sauced dumplings, which is very much on trend,
지금 트렌드인 매운 소스 만두입니다
this was something we put through our rapid innovation process.
이건 혁신적인 신속 프로세스를 통해 만든 거예요
Saucing up these dumplings, a lot of customization happening,
이런 만두에 소스를 뿌리는 트렌드가 한창 열풍이죠
and this is turning into one of our No.1's.
이게 저희 1등 상품 중 하나가 되고 있어요
For example, if we’re making fried rice with mandu,
예를 들어 우리가 볶음밥과 만두를 만들면
they must be the best.
그게 최고여야 합니다
That's my philosophy.
그게 제 철학이에요
And they must be the first.
그리고 최초여야 합니다
To that end, we must zero in on trends.
그러려면 트렌드를 잡아야 해요
We must make the very first product. And if you are sometimes late,
혹시 최초가 아니라면
if you're the second, then it must be totally different from the existing players.
기존 플레이어들과 완전히 달라야 합니다
In other words, we must always be No.1 in the area which we are in.
다시 말해 우리가 있는 분야에서 항상 1위여야 합니다
Outstanding competitiveness over our rivals.
경쟁사 대비 탁월한 경쟁력
That's what we must focus on as our target.
그게 우리가 집중해야 할 부분이고 우리의 목표입니다
There's a lot of, you know, various pieces of the CJ world.
CJ에는 정말 다양한 사업들이 있습니다.
How did teams have worked together across those businesses
서로 다른 사업부의 팀들이 어떻게 함께 일했고
to bring things together?
어떻게 시너지를 만들어냈는지에 대한 사례가 궁금합니다
I said based on the lifestyle.
저는 ‘라이프스타일’ 기반으로 말합니다
That means, people think it makes sense.
사람들도 그게 자연스럽다고 느낍니다
So for example, food and drama doesn't match, people think.
예를 들어 음식과 드라마는 원래 안 어울린다고 생각할 수 있지만
But when you see in K-dramas, they eat ramyun.
K드라마를 보면서 라면을 먹잖아요?
They use the OLIVE YOUNG cosmetics, right?
드라마에 나온 올리브영 화장품도 자연스럽게 사용합니다
So it's all connected.
결국 모든 것이 서로 연결되어 있습니다
Like we all get together and get the synergy.
모두가 함께 모여 시너지를 만들어내는 방식입니다
How do you see the leadership capabilities,
리더십 역량, 적합한 인재상
you know, the right talent profile, and what are those sort of key cultural elements
그리고 핵심적인 문화 요소를 어떻게 보시는지에 대한 질문입니다
that really give you confidence,
이 팀이든, 조직 내 다른 팀이든, 어떤 팀을 보셨을 때
whether it be this team or any other team in the organization,
‘이 팀은 다음 단계로 갈 준비가 되어 있다’고
that you look at to make sure we're ready for this next step?
확신하게 만드는 요소가 무엇인지 궁금합니다
Something I was a little bit, not surprised, rather really satisfied was
제가 놀랐다기보다는 매우 만족했던 부분이 있습니다
all my, using the important keywords or
제가 중요하게 생각하는 키워드들
like what I mentioned through Greg,
그리고 오늘 그래프를 통해 언급했던 내용들이
was already in your mind.
이미 여러분 마음속에 들어와 있다는 점이었습니다
Those kinds of things made me think, 'Oh, this is real potential.'
그런 모습을 보면서 저는 “아, 이 팀에는 정말 가능성이 있구나”라고 느꼈습니다
Good attitude and the way you're speaking together is like eager to communicate,
태도도 좋고, 서로 이야기하는 방식에서도 소통하고자 하는 의지
eager to make something,
무언가를 만들어내고자 하는 의지
and cooperate kind of mind or circumstance, can see it.
그리고 협력하려는 마음과 분위기가 느껴집니다
I all the time say we are a life company.
저는 항상 우리가 ‘라이프스타일 기업’이라고 말합니다
As you know that we are not only food
우리는 식품 뿐만 아니라
but also health and beauty and style and convenience,
건강, 뷰티, 스타일 그리고 편리함까지 아우르고 있습니다
so many cultural things.
다양한 문화사업도 하고 있습니다
That becomes a very strong weapon to win in the food market, too.
이것은 식품 시장에서 이기기 위한 매우 강력한 무기가 됩니다
We are not only just a food company.
우리는 단순한 식품회사가 아닙니다
We are a food company with lifestyle.
우리는 라이프스타일을 가진 식품회사입니다
That’s a really good chance.
이것은 정말 큰 기회입니다
Because, as you know, the K-wave is a huge trend in the States and worldwide,
K-Wave는 미국뿐 아니라 전 세계적으로 거대한 트렌드가 되고 있습니다
so you have a good chance.
그래서 우리에게는 좋은 기회가 있습니다
We must do all time the first.
우리는 항상 최초가 되어야 합니다
We must do the best.
우리는 최고가 되어야 합니다
If you are a little late, you must differentiate.
만약 조금 늦었다면 반드시 차별화해야 합니다
That means in the food market, someday you must be a No.1 and the best company
즉 식품 시장에서 언젠가 우리는 넘버원이자 최고의 회사가 되어야 하고
and totally different from other companies.
다른 회사들과는 완전히 달라야 합니다
This is not just a dream.
이것은 단순한 꿈이 아닙니다
I believe we can make it.
저는 우리가 해낼 수 있다고 믿습니다
We have a chance.
우리에게는 기회가 있습니다
We have the weapons.
우리에게는 무기가 있습니다
So we will definitely win.
그래서 우리는 반드시 이길 것입니다
Next year, you will see that.
내년에는, 우리가 식품 시장에서
We're going to be the company with the highest growth rate in the food market.
가장 높은 성장률을 기록하는 회사라는 것을 보게 될 것입니다
You can do it, right?
할 수 있죠?
I think the vision is really to help bring that product to more people in the US.
제 비전은 미국 내 더 많은 사람에게 한식을 알리는 겁니다
But as we build and innovate,
우리가 혁신을 거듭하면 사람들이 제품을 이용하고
and ultimately experiencing Korean food.
궁극적으로 한식을 경험하는 속도는 빨라질 것입니다
We've become No.1 in frozen pizza in the US,
우리는 미국 냉동 피자 업계에서 1위를 달성했습니다
but I'm inspired by further embracing the "we who prove it" mindset
피자의 역사가 그랬던 것처럼 하고잡이 정신을 더 포용하고
and using that mindset to fuel our growth into the future.
미래 성장의 원동력을 삼을 것입니다